Mario Luciano Bruno

200 Q Street NE Apt 2432 Washington, D.C. 20002 Phone: 510-386-2500 mbrunostem@gmail.com

Profile

I am a highly driven individual and have been working in education for the past 6 years. I am currently enrolled in a fullstack coding course via Georgia Tech, and looking to move my career in a different direction. I work well in collaborative environments, as well as taking accountability for my independent responsibilities. I have a passion for learning new things and sharing my knowledge with others.

Work Experience

2020 - Present. Rocketship Legacy Prep, Washington, D.C. Kindergarten STEM Teacher

- Teaching STEM lessons pertaining to the fluency levels defined by our curriculum.
- Tracking all STEM fluency and assessment test data in our tracker.
- Creating my own lesson plans that correspond to the fluency defined by our curriculum.
- Facilitating focused tutor sessions for students who need or want more practice.

2019 – 2020. Enriched D.C., Washington, D.C. Guest Educator

- Communicating with the school's point of contact.
- Filling both lead and support teaching positions as needed.
- Following the lesson plan provided by the teacher For whom I am substituting.
- Having my own lesson plan prepared in the event one is not provided.

2018 – 2019. Sherman Elementary School, San Francisco, Ca Paraprofessional

- Providing classroom support for the K-2 mild to moderate SDC.
- Mainstreaming students from the K-2 mild to moderate SDC.
- Providing one-on-one support to students in mainstream classrooms.
- Leading the K-2 mild to moderate SDC for enrichment classes.

2017 – 2018. Sherman Elementary School, San Francisco, Ca Computer Lab Teacher

- Creating lesson plans for the Digital Citizenship curriculum.
- Creating lesson plans for the Computer Science curriculum.
- Integrating Ed Tech into the mainstream classrooms.
- Applying to and being the point of contact for the Computer Science and Digital Citizenship cohort.

2016 – 2017. Higher Ground After School, Oakland, Ca Enrichment Teacher & Assistant Site Coordinator

- Providing homework support as well as one on one tutoring.
- Creating lesson plans for the poetry enrichment class I taught.
- Developing weekly and monthly enrichment activity schedules for the entire after school program.
- Maintaining daily operations of the after school program.

Education

2018 - 2019. San Francisco City College, San Francisco, Ca

2012 - 2015. Ohlone Community College, Fremont, Ca

Certificates

- District Assessment for Instructional Aides Certificate
- DC Mandated Reporter

References

Recommendations Letters available upon request